Guide to the Vassar College Women's Studies Program Records, 1977-2007
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series V. Grants and Studies
  - Mellon Core Group, 1986 (Folder 5.24)
  - Mellon Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Folder 5.25)
  - Mellon Grant, 1985-1986 (Folder 5.26)
  - Mellon Grant, 1988 (Folder 5.27)
  - Mellon Grant, 1990 (Folder 5.28)
  - Mellon Group, 1990 (Folder 5.29)
  - Mellon Seminars, 1986 (Folder 5.30)
  - Mellon Study Questionnaires, undated (Folder 5.31)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Grant (Folder 5.32)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Grant, 1983-1984 (Folder 5.33)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) Grant, 1985-1986 (Folder 5.34)
  - Wheaton Co-Education and Women's College, 1986 (Folder 5.35)
  - Wheaton Conference, undated (Folder 5.36)
  - Women's Health Initiative, 1989-1990 (Folder 5.37)
  - Women's Health Initiative Computers, 1989 (Folder 5.38)
  - Women's Health Initiative Conferences on Nutrition, 1987 (Folder 5.39)
  - Women's Health Initiative Consultants, 1988 (Folder 5.40)
  - Women's Health Initiative Correspondence, 1989 (Folder 5.41)
  - Women's Health Initiative Feasibility Studies, 1989 (Folder 5.42)
  - (Women's Health Initiative) Ann Gardon, undated (Folder 5.43)
  - Women's Health Initiative Hartmann Fund Grant, 1988 (Folder 5.44)
  - Women's Health Initiative Heath Statistics of Women College Graduates, 1985 (Folder 5.45)
  - Women's Health Initiative Hewlett-Mellon Grant, 1987 (Folder 5.46)
  - Women's Health Initiative Meetings and Notes, 1987-1990 (Folder 5.47)
  - (Women's Health Initiative) Euthenics at Vassar Rebecca Mitchell, undated (Folder 5.48)
  - (Women's Health Initiative) Morgenthau, Joan, undated (Folder 5.49)
  - (Women's Health Initiative) Rayna Rapp, undated (Folder 5.50)
  - (Women's Health Initiative) Rockefeller Foundation, undated (Folder 5.51)
  - (Women's Health Initiative) Judith Rodin, undated (Folder 5.52)
  - Women's Health Initiative Study Group, undated (Folder 5.53)
  - Women's Health Initiative Study Group - Schedules, undated (Folder 5.54)
  - Women's Health Initiative Summer Project, 1989 (Folder 5.55)
  - Women's Health Initiative Summer Schedules, undated (Folder 5.56)
- Series VI. Organizations and Other Women's Studies Programs
  - Inquiries, 1981-1982 (Folder 5.57)
  - Inquiries Regarding Course Offerings, undated (Folder 5.58)
  - Inquiries (Program and Positions), 1984-1985 (Folder 5.59)
  - Inquiries (Program and Positions), 1985-1986 (Folder 5.60)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Folder 5.61)
  - National Organization of Women, undated (Folder 5.62)
  - National Women's Studies Association, 1983-1984 (Folder 5.63)
  - National Women's Studies Association, 1985-1986 (Folder 5.64)
  - Princeton (Women's Studies), 1982-1988 (Folder 5.65)
  - Requests for Information, undated (Folder 5.66)
  - Women's Directory, undated (Folder 5.67)
  - Women's Networks, undated (Folder 5.68)
  - Women's Studies Associations, 1979-1980 (Folder 5.69)
  - Women's Studies Offerings in Other Colleges, undated (Folder 5.70)
  - Women's Studies Programs at other Colleges and Universities, 1988 (Folder 5.71)
  - York University, 1987 (Folder 5.72)
- Series VII. Miscellaneous Subject Files
  - Admissions, undated (Folder 6.1)
  - Athletics, undated (Folder 6.2)
  - Bibliographies of Women, undated (Folder 6.3)
  - Coeducation, ca. 1975-1984 (Folder 6.4)
  - Committee for Coeducation for the Future, 1978-1979 (Folder 6.5)
  - Committee to End Sexual Harassment, undated (Folder 6.6)
  - Consciousness Raising, undated (Folder 6.7)
  - Dean of the Faculty H. Patrick Sullivan, undated (Folder 7.1)
  - Extracurricular Activities, undated (Folder 7.2)
  - Feminist Transformation of the Academy, undated (Folder 7.3)
  - Feminist Union, undated (Folder 7.4)
  - Gay Issues, undated (Folder 7.5)
  - H.B. Stanton Club, undated (Folder 7.6)
  - Harriet Stanton Club, undated (Folder 7.7)
  - Packet Contents, 1997 (Folder 7.8)
  - Publishers, undated (Folder 7.9)
  - Sexual Harassment Committee, 1979 (Folder 7.10)
  - Summer Plans, undated (Folder 7.11)
  - Svoboda, Lisa, undated (Folder 7.12)
  - Women and Politics, undated (Folder 7.13)
  - Women and Science, undated (Folder 7.14)
  - Women and Work, undated (Folder 7.15)
  - Women in Anthropology, undated (Folder 7.16)
  - Women in Science Program, undated (Folder 7.17)